subtitle
I hope you don't mind me
taking the liberty.
I was careful not to drag in any dirt.
I don't mind the dirt.
I do mind...
...unannounced visits.
You police?
Are you Sapper Morton?
Civic number NK68514?
- I'm a farmer.
- I saw that.
What do you farm?
It's a protein farm.
Wallace design.
Is that what I smell?
Grow that just for me.
Garlic.
Go on, try some.
No, thank you.
I prefer to keep an empty stomach
until the hard part of the day is done.
How long you been here?
Since 2020.
But you haven't always been a farmer,
have you?
Your bag.
It's colonial medical use.
Military issue.
Where were you? Calantha?
Must have been brutal.
Plan on taking me in?
Let them take a look inside?
Mr. Morton...
...if taking you in is an option...
...I would much prefer that
to the alternative.
I'm sure you knew
it would be someone in time.
I'm sorry it had to be me.
Good as any.
Now, if you don't mind...
...if you could just look up
and to the left, please.
Please don't get up.
How's it feel killing your own kind?
I don't retire my own kind
because we don't run.
Only older models do.
And you new models
are happy scraping the shit...
...because you've never seen a miracle.
Just photograph everything.
Madam, please.
Incoming L.A.P.D. re-codec hash.
You're hurt. I'm not paying for that.
- I'll glue it.
- And?
One of the tail-end Nexus 8s.
He looks like he could take
your head off.
He tried.
He went AWOL after Calantha...
...with a few more in his outfit
I wouldn't mind closing out.
- Just him?
- Just him.
Come on home for your baseline.
One moment, madam.
30 meters to maximum depth.
What is that?
I'll send a dig team.
Come on home before the storm.
Officer KD6 -3.7.
- Let's begin. Ready?
- Yes, sir.
Recite your baseline.
And blood-black nothingness
began to spin.
A system of cells interlinked
within cells...
...interlinked within cells
interlinked within one stem.
Fuck off, skin-job.
And dreadfully distinct against the dark,
a tall white fountain played.
- Cells.
Have you ever been
in an institution? Cells.
- Do they keep you in a cell? Cells.
- Cells.
When you're not performing your duties,
do they keep you in a little box? Cells.
- Interlinked.
What's it like to hold the hand
of someone you love? Interlinked.
Did they teach you how to feel
finger to finger? Interlinked.
Do you long for having
your heart interlinked? Interlinked.
- Do you dream about being interlinked?
- Interlinked.
What's it like to hold your child
in your arms? Interlinked.
Do you feel that there's a part of you
that's missing? Interlinked.
- Within cells interlinked.
Why don't you say that three times?
Within cells interlinked.
We're done.
Constant K.
You can pick up your bonus.
Thank you, sir.
Caution, keep clear.
Connect to Off-world any time,
any place.
Packages start at 20 minutes.
Many options available.
Joi goes anywhere you want her to go.
Connect to Off-world any time,
any place.
Packages start at 20 minutes.
K? I didn't hear you. You're early.
You want me to come back?
- Just go scrub.
- Yes, ma'am.
How was your meeting?
The usual.
How was your day?
I'm getting cabin fever.
99.9 percent detoxified water.
I had an accident at work.
I think I ruined my shirt.
I'm sure I can fix that for you.
Let me take a look at it.
I need a drink.
- Do you want a drink first?
- Pour me one, will you?
I'm trying a new recipe.
I just need a bit more practice.
Don't fuss.
I should have marinated it longer.
I hope it isn't dry.
Did you know this song was released
in 1966 on Reprise Records?
It was number one on the charts.
It won't be much longer.
Just putting on the finishing touches.
Okay, it's ready.
I hope you're gonna like it.
I told you not to fuss.
And yet...
Voila! Bon appetit.
I missed you, baby sweet.
Honey, it's beautiful.
Just put your feet up.
Relax.
Was a day?
It was a day.
Would you read to me?
It'll make you feel better.
- You hate that book.
- I don't wanna read either.
Let's dance.
Do you wanna dance,
or do you wanna open your present?
What present?
- This one.
- What's the occasion?
Let's just say...
- ...it's our anniversary.
- Is it?
No, but let's just say that it is.
Okay?
Happy anniversary.
An emanator.
Thank you.
Honey, you can go anywhere you want
in the world now.
Where do you wanna go first?
I'm so happy when I'm with you.
You don't have to say that.
The dig's come through.
We have a new lead.
Get down here.
Carbon read: 14.6 GPH.
Your box is a military footlocker,
issued to Sapper Morton...
...creatively repurposed as an ossuary:
a box of bones.
Nothing else in it but hair.
The soil samples indicate
that she's been buried for 30 years.
Bones all dismantled, fully cleaned,
meticulously laid to rest.
"She"?
Cause of death, Coco?
No breaks, no sign of trauma, except...
...a fracture through the ilium.
It's a narrow birth canal.
Baby must have got stuck.
She was pregnant?
So he didn't kill her?
She died in childbirth.
What's that?
Go back.
Closer.
What's that?
Notching in the iliac crest.
It's fine-point, like a scalpel.
That looks like an emergency C-section.
The cuts are clean.
No sign of a struggle.
He was a combat medic. Maybe he tried
to save her, and he just couldn't.
He didn't seem like the saving type.
He went to the trouble of burying her.
A sentimental skin-job.
Sorry.
So where's the kid?
You scan the whole field?
Just dirt and worms. No other bodies.
Maybe he ate it.
That's not possible.
She was a Replicant.
Pregnant.
The world is built on a wall.
It separates kind.
Tell either side there's no wall,
you bought a war.
Or a slaughter.
So what you saw...
...didn't happen.
Yes, madam.
It is my job to keep order.
That's what we do here. We keep order.
You want it gone?
Erase everything.
- Even the child?
- All trace.
You have anything more to say?
I've never retired something
that was born before.
What's the difference?
To be born is to have a soul, I guess.
Are you telling me no?
I wasn't aware
that was an option, madam.
Attaboy.
Hey. You've been getting on fine
without one.
What's that, madam?
A soul.
And you new models
are happy scraping the shit...
...because you've never seen a miracle.
Just checking in on an old serial number.
Confirmation DNA?
I got hair.
An old one.
Pre-Blackout.
That's gonna be tough.
Not much from then.
And what's there is...
...thick milky.
You can customize them
as much as you'd like.
As human as you want them to be.
But your operation is strictly
a drill site, isn't it?
I wouldn't waste your money
on intelligence, attachment or appeal.
Unless you'd like to add
some pleasure models to your order.
Would it be possible
to reschedule this call, please?
Everyone remembers where they were
at the Blackout. You?
That was a little before my time.
I was home with my folks,
then 10 days of darkness.
Every machine stopped cold.
When the lights came back,
we were wiped clean.
Photos, files, every bit of data, gone.
Bank records too.
Didn't mind that.
It's funny it's only paper that lasted.
I mean, we had everything on drives.
Everything, everything, everything.
My mom still cries
over the lost baby pictures.
Well, it's a shame.
You must have been adorable.
Pretty fractured. Not much on it.
One of the last gens, pre-Prohibition.
Standard issue.
- Made by Tyrell.
- And?
Unremarkable.
"Unremarkable"?
There must be something else
we can find for him.
Another prodigal serial number returns.
A 30-year-old open case finally closed.
Thank you, officer.
I'm here for Mr. Wallace. I'm Luv.
He named you.
Must be special.
I'm here for Mr. Wallace.
Follow me.
The ancient models give
the entire endeavor a bad name.
What a gift, don't you think,
from Mr. Wallace to the world?
The outer colonies would never have
flourished had he not bought Tyrell...
...revivified the technology.
To say the least of what we do.
I see you're also a customer.
Are you satisfied with our product?
She's very realistic. Thank you.
Here. All the junk is in here.
Lucky for you,
Mr. Wallace is a data hoarder.
No one's been down here in ages.
Sorry about that.
All our memory bearings from the time.
They were all damaged in the Blackout.
But there are sometimes fragments.
You got a little boy. He shows you his
butterfly collection, plus the killing jar.
I'd take him to the doctor.
- There's a wasp crawling on your arm.
- I'd kill it.
You're reading a magazine. You come
across a full-page nude photo of a girl.
Is this testing whether I'm a Replicant
or a lesbian, Mr. Deckard?
Just answer the questions, please.
It was unclear what she was,
at least to someone.
This was a test.
We were difficult to spot then.
Was there anything unusual
about how you found her?
To warrant an official investigation?
You know how people are
about old serial numbers.
Everyone just sleeps better
when they know where they got to.
She likes him.
Who?
This Officer Deckard.
She's trying to provoke him.
It is invigorating
being asked personal questions.
Makes one feel...
...desired.
Do you enjoy your work, officer?
Please thank Mr. Wallace for your time.
You worked with Officer Deckard...
...back in the day.
What can you tell me about him?
He liked to work alone.
So did I.
So we worked together
to keep it that way.
That was it.
Anything else you can tell me?
He wasn't long for this world.
How so?
Something in his eyes.
Any idea how I could contact him?
None.
He's nyugdijas.
Retired.
What happened?
Probably got what he wanted.
To be alone.
Welcome back, sir.
You wanted to review the new model,
sir, before shipment?
An angel should never enter
the kingdom of heaven...
...without a gift.
Can you at least pronounce,
"A child is born"?
A new model.
Well, let us see her, then.
The first thought...
...one tends to fear...
...to preserve the clay.
It's fascinating.
Before we even know what we are...
...we fear to lose it.
Happy birthday.
Now, let's have a look at you.
We make angels...
...in the service of civilization.
Yes, there were bad angels once.
I make good angels now.
That is how I took us
to 9 new worlds.
9.
A child can count to 9 on fingers.
We should own the stars.
Yes, sir.
Every leap of civilization was built off
the back of a disposable workforce.
We lost our stomach for slaves...
...unless engineered.
But I can only make so many.
That barren pasture...
...empty...
...and salted...
...right here.
The dead space between the stars.
And this, the seat
that we must change for heaven.
I cannot breed them.
So help me, I have tried.
We need more Replicants
than can ever be assembled.
Millions, so we can be trillions more.
We could storm Eden and retake her.
Tyrell's final trick:
Procreation.
Perfected, then lost.
But there is a child.
Bring it to me.
Sir.
The best angel of all.
Aren't you, Luv?
The man with the green jacket.
The one who killed Sapper.
Find out what he knows.
Hi.
Hello, hello, A-Boy.
You alone?
It's fine.
Wanna buy a lady a cigarette?
Oh, you don't even smile.
Didn't you hear your friends?
Don't you know what I am?
Yeah.
Guy eating rice.
What's that?
It's a tree.
Never seen a tree before.
It's pretty.
It's dead.
Now, who keeps a dead tree?
You're not gonna kill me, are you?
Depends. What's your model number?
Why don't you look under my eye
and find out?
You don't like real girls.
Well, I'm always here.
Hi.
You can't take those.
Of course not. Proper channels
and paperwork. It's all here.
Hold this for me.
Yep. Here you go.
Coco is dead.
Bones are gone.
It's out. Already out.
How long did that take?
So, what do you have for me?
And don't say nothing.
I found that.
A sock?
- Where'd you find it?
- Sapper's.
Anything else?
I burned everything else.
Then what's this? What's that date?
Is that a birthday? A death day?
I don't know yet.
Am I the only one that can see
the fucking sunrise here?
This breaks the world, K.
You know, I've known a lot of your kind.
All useful, but with you,
I sometimes forget.
We didn't have any of you
where I was a kid.
Do you remember anything?
Before you were under me,
you have any memories from before?
I have memories...
...but they're not real.
They're just implants.
Tell me one.
From when you were a kid.
I feel strange sharing a childhood story,
considering I was never a child.
Well, would it help you share
if I told you it was an order?
I have one about a toy that I had.
A wooden horse.
With an inscription underneath.
All I remember is a group of boys
trying to take it away from me.
So I run.
I go looking for a place to hide it,
and the only place is this dark furnace.
It's very dark, and I'm very scared...
...but this horse is all I have,
so I go in anyway.
Later on, those kids find me...
...and they beat me to tell them
where it is, but I don't.
That's it.
Little K, fighting for what's his.
It's a good one.
Look at me.
We're all just looking out
for something real.
What happens if I finish that?
Shouldn't I get back to work, madam?
Check back in after DNA base.
Officer KD6 -3.7.
Request.
DNA records: children born 6-10-21.
Looking for anomalies.
You have the satcrystal backup?
Okay.
Run it raw.
Mere data makes a man.
A and C and T and G.
The alphabet of you.
All from four symbols.
I'm only two:
One and zero.
Half as much but twice as elegant,
sweetheart.
You don't prefer your madam?
You were listening.
Maybe.
You didn't like her enough
to tell her the truth.
6, 10 and 21.
There's nothing to tell.
How many times
have you told me that story?
Your memory?
The date carved beneath.
6, 10 and 21.
Coincidence?
A dangerous coincidence.
I always knew you were special.
Maybe this is how.
A child.
Of woman born.
Pushed into the world.
Wanted.
Loved.
Well, if it were true...
...I'd be hunted for the rest of my life
by someone just like me.
It's okay to dream a little.
- Isn't it?
- Not if you're us.
Stop.
Put up 4847 and 2181 side-by-side.
They're identical. Translate.
A boy and a girl.
- It's impossible.
- Why?
Two people can't have identical DNA.
One of these isn't real. It's a copy.
They were both processed
at the Morrill Cole Orphanage.
It says the girl died there.
Genetic disorder.
Galatians Syndrome.
And the boy...
...disappears.
Where's the orphanage?
You wanna go for a ride?
Well, here we are.
Buckle up.
K?
K? K?
K? K? K?
Stay back.
Fire again.
Fire.
200 feet to the east.
Go north.
Fire.
Stop. 20 degrees east.
Stop.
Zoom in.
Closer.
Oh, come on.
Get up.
Do your fucking job.
Find the child.
Watch the car.
Every last piece, or I'll put you outside
where the sky is raining...
...where it's raining fire!
You're in here to work.
And if you're not working,
I don't need you.
I don't need any of...
Hi.
The nickel is for the colonial ships.
Closest any of them
or any of us is gonna get...
...to that grand life Off-world.
And I encourage play, I do.
Keeps them occupied...
...and it makes them nimble, right?
But it's work.
It's work that molds them
into a child worth having.
So come on, now.
What sort do you have in mind?
Because I got all kinds.
- Oh, no, no, no.
- I'm not buying.
No, no, no. This is just my game,
and I play it fair.
No. No, I mean, bigger than you...
Bigger than you have tried
to shut me down. Bigger than you.
And they were men, at that.
A little boy came through here
about 30 years back.
I need to see your records.
Legitimate placements,
private sales, everything.
Don't keep records that far back.
- You don't?
- I don't.
Sorry.
Can't help you.
- You can't?
- Nope.
I think you can.
I think someone like you
keeps a long memory.
Now you can tell me
what you remember...
...or I can put a hole right here
and take a look.
They were laughing and what was it
you said? What'd you say?
Are you coming?
Where is it?
Oh, God.
Where, where, where?
I don't see it. Here.
It's gone.
It's the entire year.
I didn't do that.
That wasn't me.
I didn't. Wasn't me.
I always told you.
You're special.
Born.
Not made.
Hidden with care.
A real boy now.
A real boy needs a real name.
Joe.
"Joe"?
You're too important for K.
Your mother would've named you.
Joe.
- Joe.
- Stop.
How do I know
if a memory is an implant or not?
Who makes the memories?
Dr. Ana Stelline?
A visitor.
Is that okay?
Yes.
It's just unusual.
Nice to meet you, Officer KD6 -3.7.
Sorry.
It's a compromised immune system.
A life of freedom,
so long as it's behind glass.
- Is that why you're not Off-world?
- Yes.
My parents had our passes in pocket,
but I took sick.
So it was a new life for me.
And they put me in my cage...
...filled it with everything they could
to keep me happy.
Except company, of course.
And I was used to crowds.
What can I help you with?
Thought you might be able to help me
with a case.
Oh, that's the most interesting thing
I've been offered to help with in ages.
Do you mind if I work while you talk?
Of course.
I promise I hear every word.
They say you're
the best memory-maker there is.
Well, then, they're kind.
I love birthday parties.
You work for Wallace?
Subcontract. I'm one of his suppliers.
He offered to buy me out,
but I take my freedom where I can find it.
Why are you so good?
What makes your memories
so authentic?
Well, there's a bit of every artist
in their work.
But I was locked
in a sterile chamber at 8...
...so if I wanted to see the world,
I had to imagine it.
Got very good at imagining.
Wallace needs my talent
to maintain a stable product.
I think it's only kind.
Replicants live such hard lives,
made to do what we'd rather not.
I can't help your future...
...but I can give you good memories
to think back on and smile.
It's nice.
It's better than nice.
It feels authentic.
And if you have authentic memories,
you have real human responses.
Wouldn't you agree?
Are they all constructed,
or do you ever use ones that are real?
It's illegal to use real memories, officer.
How can you tell the difference?
Can you tell if something...
...really happened?
They all think it's about more detail.
But that's not how memory works.
We recall with our feelings.
Anything real should be a mess.
I can show you.
Sit.
Now, think about the memory
you want me to see.
Not even that hard. Just picture it.
Let it play.
Someone lived this, yes.
This happened.
I know it's real.
Goddamn it!
Officer KD6 -3.7.
Madam is calling you in.
You're under arrest.
Drop your gun and keep your hands
where I can see them.
- Cells.
Have you ever been
in an institution? Cells.
When you're not performing your duties,
do they keep you in a little box? Cells.
- Interlinked.
What's it like to hold the hand
of someone you love?
- Interlinked.
- Within cells interlinked.
- Within the cells interlinked.
What's it like
to be filled with dread? Dreadfully.
Do you like being separated
from other people? Distinct.
- Dreadfully distinct. Dark.
- Within cells interlinked.
- Within the cells interlinked.
- Within one stem.
- And dreadfully distinct.
- Against the dark.
- A tall white fountain played.
You're not even close to baseline.
Out! And close the door.
What the fuck is with you?
I put you on a case.
I impressed on you
the importance of that case...
...and then we pick you up fucking
around outside an upgrade center?
Scan said you didn't look like you
on the inside. Miles off your baseline.
- Do you know what that means?
- I found the kid.
He was set up like a standard Replicant,
put on a service job.
Even he didn't know who he was.
- And?
- And it's done.
- What does that mean, "it's done"?
- What you asked.
It's done.
Fuck.
You just stopped a bomb from going off.
You did good.
I can help you get out
of this station alive...
...but you have 48 hours
to get back on track.
Surrender your gun and badge.
And your next baseline test
is out of my hands.
Thank you, madam.
You were right.
You were right about everything.
Thought you weren't interested,
worky man.
You liked her. I could tell.
It's okay.
She's real.
I wanna be real for you.
You are real for me.
You have a special lady here.
Okay.
Let's do it.
Look at you.
Quiet now, I have to sync.
Joi is anything you want her to be.
Joi goes anywhere
you want her to go.
99.9 percent detoxified water.
It's from a tree.
I'm done with you.
You can go now.
Quiet now.
I've been inside you.
Not so much there as you think.
Coffee?
They'll be coming after me soon.
I'm coming with you.
But not like this.
If they come here looking for you,
they'll have access to all my memories.
You have to delete me
from the console.
My present.
Put me there.
I can't do that.
Think about it:
If anything happens to this, that's it.
You're gone.
Yes.
Like a real girl.
Please.
Joe, please.
I want this.
But I can't do it myself.
Break the antenna.
I don't need a real horse.
I just wanna find out where it's from.
Radiation from a reactor?
It matches a dirty bomb.
There's only one place that dirty.
Nobody lives there.
Go to 5.
4, 30 degrees to the left.
Tilt up.
Elevate to 400 feet.
Radiation analysis.
Move forward.
Tilt up.
Stop.
Move forward.
Go to 5.
7, move forward.
6.
Stop.
Go to 7.
8.
9.
Heat analysis.
Life.
What is it?
Guess we're about to find out.
Too dark in here.
I like him.
He's a good boy.
Where is he?
I have no idea. He's off-duty.
Check around.
I checked...
...anywhere a good boy might go.
You're too late.
It's gone.
He destroyed it.
Everything about it.
Well, except for the box of bones
that you already took.
Which, I'll wager, wasn't enough.
Here you are.
You tiny thing.
In the face of the fabulous new,
your only thought is to kill it?
For fear of great change?
You can't hold the tide with a broom.
Except that I did.
Where is he?!
You're so sure.
Because he told you.
Because we never lie.
I'm gonna tell Mr. Wallace
you tried to shoot me first.
So I had to kill you.
Then do what you gotta do.
Madam.
Location: Officer KD6 -3.7.
Mightn't happen to have
a piece of cheese about you, now?
Would you, boy?
Treasure Island?
He reads.
That's good.
Me too.
Not much else to do around here
at night anymore.
Many is the night I dream of cheese...
...toasted, mostly.
What are you doing here?
I heard the piano.
Don't lie.
It's rude.
You're a cop.
- I'm not here to take you in.
- Oh, yeah?
Then, what?
I just have some questions.
What questions?
Stay.
Look, I don't wanna hurt you.
But you're not making it easy.
I like this song.
We could keep at this,
or we could get a drink.
I'll take the drink.
This is really something.
The whole town was something.
One time.
Forget your troubles...
...see a show...
...gamble a little.
Win some money, lose some money.
They made money seem like candy.
You like whiskey?
I've got millions...
...of bottles of whiskey.
Here.
Bleeding.
Is it real?
I don't know.
Ask him.
You got a name?
Officer KD6 -3.7...
That's not a name.
That's a serial number.
All right.
Joe.
What do you want, Joe?
- I wanna ask you some questions.
- Like what?
Like what was her name,
the mother of your child?
What was she like?
- You two live here together?
- Too many questions.
I had your job. I was good at it.
- It was simpler then.
- Why you making it complicated?
- Why don't you answer the question?
- What question?
I didn't figure you as one for bullshit.
What's her name?
Rachael.
Her name was Rachael.
What happened to the kid?
Who put it in the orphanage?
Was it you?
I was long gone by then.
You didn't even meet your own kid?
Why?
Because that was the plan.
I showed them how to scramble
the records, cover their tracks.
Everyone had a part.
Mine was to leave.
Then the Blackout came,
paved over everything.
Couldn't have found the child if I tried.
- Did you want to?
- Not really.
- Why not?
- Because we were being hunted.
I didn't want our child found...
...taken apart, dissected.
Sometimes, to love someone...
...you gotta be a stranger.
To strangers.
What'd you do?
Who'd you bring?
- No one.
- Oh, yeah?
Target locked.
They know you're here.
I came alone.
Bad dog.
Stop.
I do hope you're satisfied
with our product.
I love...
Hey, there's someone
who wants to meet you.
You can trust us.
You must want me to look up
and to the left.
This is Freysa.
She fought with Sapper on Calantha.
I recognize you.
Did you help him hide the child?
I was there.
I saw a miracle delivered.
A perfect little face crying up at me.
Mad as thunder.
Were you with her?
Rachael?
I held her as she died.
We hid the child
and made a vow to keep our secret.
That's why Sapper let you kill him.
I knew that baby meant
we are more than just slaves.
If a baby can come from one of us...
...we are our own masters.
More human than humans.
A revolution is coming.
And we're building an army.
I want to free our people.
If you want to be free...
...join us.
Deckard, Sapper, you, me...
...our lives mean nothing
next to a storm that's coming.
Dying for the right cause
is the most human thing we can do.
You led Wallace to Deckard.
You cannot allow Deckard
to lead Wallace to me.
You must kill Deckard.
Deckard only wanted
his baby to be safe.
And she is.
When the time comes,
I will show her to the world...
...and she will lead our army.
"She"?
Of course.
Rachael had a daughter.
With my own eyes, I saw her come.
I dressed her in blue
when it was time for her to go.
It was a boy that you hid.
That is just a piece of the puzzle.
You imagined it was you?
You did.
We all wish it was us.
That's why we believe.
Someone lived this, yes.
I showed them how to scramble
the records, cover their tracks.
With my own eyes, I saw her come.
I dressed her in blue
when it was time for her to go.
There's a bit of every
artist in their work.
Always jumping, that one.
Never a thought of what to do
if it made land.
All the courage in the world
cannot alter fact.
I have wanted to meet you
for so very long.
You are a wonder to me, Mr. Deckard.
I had the lock.
I found the key.
Yet the pins do not align.
The door remains locked.
I need the specimen to reach it,
Mr. Deckard.
The child.
I need the child.
To teach them all to fly.
And God remembered Rachel...
...heeded her and opened her womb.
Do you like our owl?
It's artificial?
Of course it is.
Must be expensive.
Very. I'm Rachael.
Deckard.
Is it the same...
...now, as then...
...the moment you met her?
All these years
you looked back on that day...
...drunk on the memory
of its perfection.
How shiny her lips.
How instant your connection.
Did it never occur to you that's why
you were summoned in the first place?
Designed to do nothing short
of fall for her right then and there.
All to make that single perfect specimen.
That is, if you were designed.
Love...
...or mathematical precision.
Yes.
No.
I know what's real.
It was very clever
to keep yourself empty of information...
...and all it cost you was everything.
But you can still help me.
You had help in the hiding.
Where did they go?
I know you know something.
Help me...
...and very, very good things
can come to you.
You don't have children...
...do you?
Oh, I have millions.
You think I have nothing to offer but pain.
Only I know...
...you love pain.
Pain reminds you
the joy you felt was real.
More joy, then.
Do not be afraid.
An angel...
...made again.
For you.
Did you miss me?
Don't you love me?
Her eyes were green.
Off-world...
...I have everything I need
to make you talk.
You do not know what pain is yet.
You will learn.
Hello, handsome.
What a day.
You look lonely.
I can fix that.
You look like a good joe.
Dying for the right cause
is the most human thing we can do.
Because you've never seen a miracle.
You're entering Los Angeles Airport
restricted airspace.
Confirm your identity.
Transport S-14-4-XD. Confirmed.
Space, this is 0-6.
Outbound departure, route 0-3-0.
Where are we going?
Home.
Drive two down.
Backup engaged.
Warning.
- Can we make it?
- We're too low!
Take us back!
Get us up.
Open the door.
I'm the best one.
Off-world is waiting.
Joe. Joe!
Joe!
You should have let me die out there.
You did.
You drowned out there.
You're free to meet your daughter now.
All the best memories are hers.
Why?
Who am I to you?
Go meet your daughter.
You okay?
Just a moment.
Beautiful, isn't it?